<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    
    
    <description>Thank You for visiting my homepage.</description>
    
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      <item>
        <title>Dynamic arguments in argparse subparser</title>
        <description>
          A basic guide to manipulating python&apos;s ArgumentParser object at your will - 
          Past month, while working on some command-line tool written in python based on argparse, I was faced with task of adding some new arguments to extend some functionality. The only problem was the number and name of arguments were dynamic, i.e., they depended on the value supplied to some other...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2023-09-18-dynamic-arguments-argparse-subparser/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2023-09-18-dynamic-arguments-argparse-subparser/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>bug.log.1</title>
        <description>
          the safe way to model object creation with django-ninja - 
          Starting a series where I would be compiling some of the bugs I run into during my software development projects. These bugs have usually given me a hard time since there seems to be nothing wrong at face value, but on deeper analysis, they expose some conceptual mistake on my...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2023-03-29-bug-log-1/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2023-03-29-bug-log-1/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Journey to Japan 🇯🇵</title>
        <description>
          井の中の蛙大海を知らず。 - 
          The phrase in the subtitle loosely translates to “a frog in the small well is unaware of the mighty ocean”, referring to the state of being trapped by one’s own narrow knowledge and ideas, and not knowing that there is a wider world out there. So on a mission to...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2023-02-20-japan/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2023-02-20-japan/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Codrop: Code-n-Drop</title>
        <description>
          A File-Sharing &lt;a href=&quot;https://marketplace.visualstudio.com/items?itemName=gurbaaz.codrop&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;VS Code Extension 📦&lt;/a&gt; - 
          Around a month back, after the end semester examinations of my 7th semester were over and before the placement season was about to begin, I was looking for some random inspiration to build some cool stuff. During that period, one of my friends was working on some piece of code...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2023-01-16-codrop/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2023-01-16-codrop/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Demystifying the Docker</title>
        <description>
          A Learning Curve - 
          You wake up one day to build some cool web app or an ML model, motivate yourself a step further to deploy it or atleast share with your friends. On googling what to do now, you are bombarded with various methodologies and terminologeies. Amidst popular terms like Github, AWS, Heroku,...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2021-05-30-demystifying-the-docker/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2021-05-30-demystifying-the-docker/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>5 Kakãrs of Khalsa</title>
        <description>
          The Articles of Sikh Faith - 
          The motivation behind posting this on instagram was to create an awareness regarding one of the core part in the life of a “Amritdhari” or a borrowed term from the West, “baptised” Sikh. I have seen friends and strangers who get amused or wierdly astonished at the sight of my...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2020-06-03-5-Ks-of-kakar/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2020-06-03-5-Ks-of-kakar/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
